<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-04-19T10:09:35+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">People of NIT A</title><subtitle>/capturing the spirit of NIT Agartala, one story at a time/</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Meet me, I am Spongebob!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Spongebob/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Meet me, I am Spongebob!" /><published>2024-03-03T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2024-03-03T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Spongebob</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Spongebob/"><![CDATA[<p>Ahoy there, landlubbers! I’m SpongeBob SquarePants, the happiest sponge in all of Bikini Bottom! From the moment I popped out of my pineapple under the sea, I’ve been soaking up the sun and spreading joy like jelly on toast! <br /><br />
By day, you’ll find me flipping Krabby Patties at the Krusty Krab, where I serve up smiles with every order. But when the spatula’s down, I’m off on wild adventures with my pals Patrick, Sandy, and even my grumpy neighbor Squidward! Whether it’s jellyfishing in Jellyfish Fields or rocking out with my band at the Bubble Bowl, there’s never a dull moment in my underwater world. <br /><br />
So grab your snorkel and join me for a splash-tastic journey through the seven seas!</p>

<p><a href="https://postimg.cc/gXRRyhZ0"><img src="https://i.postimg.cc/wv4VpcxD/mgid-arc-imageassetref-shared-nick.jpg" alt="mgid-arc-imageassetref-shared-nick.jpg" /></a></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahoy there, landlubbers! I’m SpongeBob SquarePants, the happiest sponge in all of Bikini Bottom! From the moment I popped out of my pineapple under the sea, I’ve been soaking up the sun and spreading joy like jelly on toast! By day, you’ll find me flipping Krabby Patties at the Krusty Krab, where I serve up smiles with every order. But when the spatula’s down, I’m off on wild adventures with my pals Patrick, Sandy, and even my grumpy neighbor Squidward! Whether it’s jellyfishing in Jellyfish Fields or rocking out with my band at the Bubble Bowl, there’s never a dull moment in my underwater world. So grab your snorkel and join me for a splash-tastic journey through the seven seas!]]></summary></entry></feed>